this is just my reminder that y'all don't have to listen to me like i'm just a person in the world
like everybody else i have a platform and i use it to speak the things that i really feel like
are needing to be heard and that will be helpful to people that's it but folks be really trying to
like oh who does she think she is but like i'm not forcing my way into your life you on my page
and you can scroll if you see me on someone else's page it's really just unnerving
word to the michael jordans on my sweatshirt you don't have to listen to me you have a whole choice
system of your own that you can move with without having to disrespect me in the process
in christ because i had somebody to say just now oh you know amanda she figures herself some kind of
political prophet huh i'm just somebody who reads
you